// Question - JSON Format
export const question = [
  {
    questionNo: "0",
    question: "1. Who won the ICC ODI World Cup in 2011 ?",
    options: [["India", "M"], ["Australia", "F"], ["Others", "O"]],
    answer: "M",
    attemptedAnswer: "",
    answeredCorrectly: false,
    answeredRequested: false
  },
  {
    questionNo: "1",
    question: "2. Who won the Football World Cup in 2014 ?",
    options: [["France", "M"], ["Germany", "F"], ["Others", "O"]],
    answer: "F",
    attemptedAnswer: "",
    answeredCorrectly: false,
    answeredRequested: false
  },
  {
    questionNo: "2",
    question: "3. Who is also known as Master Blaster",
    options: [["Saurav", "M"], ["Sehwag", "F"], ["Sachin", "O"]],
    answer: "O",
    attemptedAnswer: "",
    answeredSubmitted: false,
    answeredRequested: false
  },
  {
    questionNo: "3",
    question: "4. Who Invented Bulb",
    options: [["Edison", "E"], ["Sandeep Gokhale", "S"], ["Other", "O"]],
    answer: "E",
    attemptedAnswer: "",
    answeredSubmitted: false,
    answeredRequested: false
  },
  {
    questionNo: "4",
    question: "5. Who Invented Zero",
    options: [
      ["Brahmagupta", "B"],
      ["Sandeep Gokhale", "S"],
      ["Aryabhatta", "O"]
    ],
    answer: "B",
    attemptedAnswer: "",
    answeredSubmitted: false,
    answeredRequested: false
  },
  {
    questionNo: "5",
    question: "6. How many hours do we have in a day?",
    options: [["24", "24"], ["25", "25"], ["26", "26"]],
    answer: "24",
    attemptedAnswer: "",
    answeredSubmitted: false,
    answeredRequested: false
  },
  {
    questionNo: "6",
    question: "7. How many days do we have in a week?",
    options: [["7", "7"], ["8", "8"], ["9", "9"]],
    answer: "7",
    attemptedAnswer: "",
    answeredSubmitted: false,
    answeredRequested: false
  },
  {
    questionNo: "7",
    question: "8. Who is the author of the inheritance cycle?",
    options: [
      ["JK Rowling", "A"],
      [" Christopher Paolini", "B"],
      [" Deepthi BG", "C"]
    ],
    answer: "B",
    attemptedAnswer: "",
    answeredSubmitted: false,
    answeredRequested: false
  },
  {
    questionNo: "8",
    question: "9. Who created the character Modesty Blaise?",
    options: [
      ["Stephen King", "A"],
      [" Peter O Donnell", "B"],
      [" JK Rowling", "C"]
    ],
    answer: "B",
    attemptedAnswer: "",
    answeredSubmitted: false,
    answeredRequested: false
  },
  {
    questionNo: "9",
    question:
      "10. The first Football world cup was held in which country in 1930?",
    options: [["Uruguay", "A"], ["Italy", "B"], ["India", "C"]],
    answer: "A",
    attemptedAnswer: "",
    answeredSubmitted: false,
    answeredRequested: false
  },
  {
    questionNo: "10",
    question: "11. Which Indian cricketing legend is also knows as The Wall?",
    options: [["Rahul Bose", "A"], [" KL Rahul", "B"], ["Rahul Dravid", "C"]],
    answer: "C",
    attemptedAnswer: "",
    answeredSubmitted: false,
    answeredRequested: false
  },
  {
    questionNo: "11",
    question: "11. Who is the first Indian formula one driver?",
    options: [
      ["Narain Karthikeyan", "A"],
      [" Sania Nehwal", "B"],
      [" Karun Chandok", "C"]
    ],
    answer: "A",
    attemptedAnswer: "",
    answeredSubmitted: false,
    answeredRequested: false
  }
];
